good evening sir my name is neha sharma
my name means affection i belong to ara
which is famous for arane devi temple
and i have done my graduation in
commerce stream
from bakewasi university with 71
my hobbies are listening music dancing
singing and as far as
my strengths are concerned i am a
hardworking person
i am punctual because i have always
value the time
and i am loyal toward my work i like
meeting
successful personalities and also
learning new thing from them
and i am a team spirit person i don't
try to hug
all the credits that's all about me
sir consists of seven members in my
family
my grandfather is head of our family and
my parents
are teacher and my elder sister is
got married and my brother is pursuing
medical exam preparation
sir i always appreciate my parents job
and i have always been fascinated in
banking finance
and teaching is very excellent job and
but for me sir my interest is always in
banking sector so i choose in
choose this sector
okay sir banking is a potential sector
and here growth opportunity is more
and a banking environment is a
make us rush free and here we
get the meeting new personalities making
new friends
as far as my hobbies and
bank also covered our monetary aspects
that is necessary for a middle class fam
middle class person like me
and also say a social repetition in this
job
sir my certain goal is to get a job in
icici bank
and my long term goal is to get a good
and respectable position in its bank
and i want to see myself
as a grade a officer in your stream
organization
salary is one of the motivational factor
and for me growth opportunity and job
satisfaction is much more important
but as a fresher i don't know
my market value but if you will make me
an offer
it will be commensurate with my
qualification and basic salary structure
in your organization
sir i believe my skill are compatible
for this job and i sure that because
i my strong interest in banking sector
i will be a key player and i assure you
you will never regret to hire me
[Music]
okay sir i work
every perfect manner this is my
weaknesses
and i give more weight as my
professional work
because of that my personal work get
hampered
so sierra is a stand for cash reserve
ratio
and uh secure our money
uh to rbi
and current sierra is three percent
so commercial bank lane money
by a central bank and that is called
a reparate
so current report rate is uh
four percent
accounting is the processing and
communication of financial and
non-financial transaction
in economic entities
so in in saving account uh
limited transaction and current account
has a no limited transaction and in
saving account
we earn interest from bank and in
current account i don't earn
any interest
obviously sir i can survive anywhere
because uh because of my adjustable
nature
and i don't any homesickness and this is
not
no problem for me to anywhere
in india